[
    [
        {
            "type": 1,
            "question": "Name the process where neural connection formation rate slows down to make the circuits more efficient?",
            "answers": 2,
            "options": [
                "Depriviation",
                "Pruning",
                "Puring",
                "Decicuiting"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 2,
            "question": "Arrange in the correct order the process of Neural Connections:",
            "answers": [
                "The early age is the most active period",
                "1 million neuron connections are made every second",
                "Rapid proliferation occurs",
                "Pruning takes place"
            ],
            "options": [
                "1 million neuron connections are made every second",
                "Rapid proliferation occurs",
                "The early age is the most active period",
                "Pruning takes place"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "Select the correct capacities which are inextricably intertwined throughout the life course and are shaped by thr basic interaction of genes and experience of a developing brain?",
            "answers": [1, 2, 4],
            "options": [
                "Cognitive",
                "Emotional",
                "Physical",
                "Social"
            ]
        }
    ],

    [
        {
            "type": 1,
            "question": "What reinforces the newly formed brain circuits?",
            "answers": 3,
            "options": [
                "Extensive Pressure",
                "Experience Repetitions",
                "Repeated Use",
                "Automatic Reinforcement"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 2,
            "question": "Arrange the steps to practice serve and return orderwise",
            "answers": [
                "Notice the serve and share the focus of attention",
                "Return the serve by supporting and encouraging",
                "Give it a name",
                "Take turns and wait to keep the interaction going"
            ],
            "options": [
                "Take turns and wait to keep the interaction going",
                "Give it a name",
                "Return the serve by supporting and encouraging",
                "Notice the serve and share the focus of attention"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "Young Children naturally reach out for interactions through?",
            "answers": [1, 3, 4],
            "options": [
                "Babbling",
                "Cellphones",
                "Gestures",
                "Expressions"
            ]
        }
    ],

    [
        {
            "type": 1,
            "question": "What is the result of Long Lasting and Extreme Stress on a childs brain with no buffering relationships?",
            "answers": 2,
            "options": [
                "Emotionless Attitude",
                "Damaged or weakend brain architecture",
                "Mental In capabilities",
                "Stronger Personality"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 2,
            "question": "What happens to the person who faces serious early adversities or such types of early age hardships for an prolonged ammount of time?",
            "answers": [
                "Percive and focus mostly on negetives such as life threats",
                "Lower Self Efficacy",
                "Lack of goal oriented behaviour",
                "Resulting in an overall slow development"
            ],
            "options": [
                "Lack of goal oriented behaviour",
                "Percive and focus mostly on negetives such as life threats",
                "Lower Self Efficacy",
                "Resulting in an overall slow development"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "How to reduce sources of stress?",
            "answers": [1, 2, 3],
            "options": [
                "Create conditions in which family can meet basic needs",
                "Pay special attention to the needs of children",
                "Provide consistent and adequate funding ",
                "Leave everyone on their own and pay attention to ourself"
            ]
        }
    ],

    [
        {
            "type": 1,
            "question": "How can children who suffer severe deprviation recover?",
            "answers": 1,
            "options": [
                "Theraputic intervention and highly supportive care",
                "Change of Living Environment to a Pleasant one ",
                "Living Alone away from previous enviorment",
                "Socialize"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "Name Some consequences of limited caregiver responsiveness",
            "answers": [2, 3, 4],
            "options": [
                "Stone cold heart",
                "Cognitive delays",
                "Stunning of physical growth",
                "Disruption of body's stress response"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": 3,
            "question": "What are some Consequences of severe depreviation?",
            "answers": [1, 2, 3],
            "options": [
                "Disrupts the child's way of thinking",
                "Alters the development of biological stress response system ",
                "Singnificant risk of emotional or interpersonal difficulties",
                "Physical incapabilities"
            ]
        }
    ]
]
